He took advantage of you.
He...
Can't you be a little more perceptive?
I...
You...
Put me down.
Sui'er,
with me around,
no one will hurt you again.
Your Royal Highness,
sends you to visit me every day
in the name of healing.
What
do you
want from me?
I'm afraid you got it wrong.
I never served
the Second Prince.
Although I'm in prison,
I'm still the Prime Minister.
No matter who your master is,
isn't it a bit rash
to kill me here?
Thank you for reminding me.
I'm not here
to kill you.
If you cooperate with me,
I won't make you suffer too much.
After all,
my master doesn't want to hurt you.
Who is the master
behind you?
[Jingxi River is perilous,]
[so people tread carefully.]
[Throughout the year,]
[there are no reports]
[of people drowning.]
[Yet in the calm waters,]
[where there are no stones,]
[we often hear]
[of someone]
[sinking...]
[Drowning...]
[Prime Minister Shen!]
Minister Shen.
Shen...
Jingxi is perilous,
so people tread carefully.
Throughout the year,
no one perishes.
Yet in the calm waters without rocks,
there are always
those who drown.
Sovereign,
what does Lord Shen
by that?
He's reminding me that
when I think everything is well planned,
it's the most dangerous time.
But
he did remind me
to pay attention
to the hidden reefs.
How's the investigation
into the person helping Sui'er?
Sovereign,
although The Second Prince
failed to capture the person who helped the princess consort,
in my opinion,
that person must have a hiding place
in Lingguo Temple.
Lingguo Temple
has always been guarded by royal guards.
I can't figure out
the identity of the other party at the moment.
Lingguo Temple?
There was a rumor
about Princess Consort of Rui.
Do you know the details?
You mean the book?
It was indeed drawn by Princess Consort of Rui.
The man in it
seems to refer to Prince Yu
at the border.
I didn't expect
Prince Yu
has been away from Kyoto for so long,
but there are still people missing him.
I remember Consort Dowager Li
lives in
Lingguo Temple, right?
That's right.
Consort Dowager Li
has been living in Lingguo Temple.
Is it Prince Yu who has been secretly
helping Princess Consort of Rui?
It seems that
we need to adjust
our plan.
This is the secret letter written by Minister Shen.
The Second Prince hasn't finished his move.
Leave it to him.
Yes.
The Second Prince has made a move.
Just now,
Your Majesty
stripped Minister Shen of his position as Prime Minister.
And
he ordered his beheading next month.
So sudden.
It is said that
a secret letter written by Minister Shen to General Xiao
was discovered.
It clearly records
Minister Shen and General Xiao's collusion with the enemy.
And
Prince Rui
just entered the palace before nightfall.
This secret letter
must be the one he took.
A secret letter in his own handwriting.
No wonder the Great Apricot Pharmacy
was abandoned so easily.
It seems they have a backup plan.
The Great Apricot Pharmacy was just destroyed,
and this new poison was made soon after.
It seems
the secret pharmaceutical facility
is near the royal city.
I'll check it out right away.
The imperial edict has been issued.
The biggest threat to him now
is not Prime Minister Shen,
but...
It's time to return to the capital.
Prince.
Miss.
Miss, you finally woke up.
You scared me to death.
How are you?
I'm fine, Zhiyan.
You've been
taking care of me these days.
I was worried that someone would find out
that you left the temple,
so I didn't tell anyone.
You were injured.
But this courtyard is remote,
and they
avoid it,
so they don't care about you.
So,
no one else?
It was Young Master Lou
who brought you back that day.
He's been
here day and night for days.
But I haven't seen him
since yesterday.
So unreliable.
I knew it was him.
Did he leave any message
or anything?
Oh, right.
His Highness sent a message.
He said...
His Highness?
What did he say?
He said
he found a secret letter from Master to the enemy.
His Majesty has decreed that he will be beheaded in a month.
It's a done deal.
He advised you
not to act impulsively.
My Lady,
no wonder you left without a word.
You also thought there was no turning back.
Is that so?
Sir,
any updates on my father's case?
Let's talk in private.
Please follow me.
Princess Consort of Rui
I have some acquaintance with Minister Shen.
I'll give you a piece of advice.
You've been waiting here for nearly ten days.
Even if he is thousands of miles away,
he should know about your deeds.
But so far,
no one has come.
You should understand the reason.
Instead of waiting here,
you'd better think about
what you're going to do
after Minister Shen's execution.
If you just want to persuade me to leave,
you don't have to waste your breath.
It's not that I'm driving you away.
I just can't help you.
Even if you break this drum,
no one will come to see you.
Fine.
Then I'll break this drum first.
I find you
have the same temper as your father.
Both of you are so stubborn.
Forget it.
If you really want to save your father,
I have a plan.
Maybe it works.
Please tell me.
Your father's case
is handled by Prince Rui.
You should know
the reason.
No one in the court
dares to go against him
except your father.
I heard that
Prince Yu,
who is far away from the border,
will return to the capital tomorrow.
He is the Emperor's brother.
Instead of waiting here,
why don't you go and ask him for help?
Maybe he can help you.
Prince Yu
has returned to the capital.
Prince Yu?
The Prince Yu who went to the border?
Prince Yu
has returned to the capital.
This is the Prince Yu who went to the border?
Didn't he say that when he left the capital eight years ago,
he vowed
he would never return?
Why did he come back suddenly?
I have a distant relative
who serves in the army.
He said
Prince Yu
is tall and fierce.
He often eats raw meat.
We can't interfere in the court affairs.
But
we'd better avoid
the mansion of Prince Yu.
Who is she?
Shen Yi, the Prime Minister,
and Xiao Wei, the general of the Western Jin,
were wronged.
They were innocent.
I'm Shen Suhe.
Yes.
I beg you
to do justice
and clear the names
of the Prime Minister and General Xiao.
I think she is wronged.
Can we help her?
It's him.
Why don't I see Young Master Lou?
Your Highness,
someone is holding a blood letter to seek justice.
Yes.
Princess Consort of Rui,
don't stay here.
Go back.
What if something happens?
I want to see more.
Don't.
His Highness ordered
you to go to the palace now.
Anyone who dares to stop you
will be punished by military law.
Shen Yi, the Prime Minister,
and Xiao Wei, the General of the Western Jin,
were framed for
colluding with the enemy.
I, Shen Suhe,
beg you to do justice
and clear the names
of them.
Shen Yi, the Prime Minister,
and Xiao Wei, the General of the Western Jin,
were framed
for treason.
It's all a lie!
Your Highness,
I beg you
to uphold justice
and clear their names!